Oh! Reznik talking smack,
I can't even respond to that.
You ok?
Do I look ok?
If you were any thinner, you wouldn't exist.
What's wrong?
I don't know, deja vu.
You are tired, you need to sleep.
How do you do it?
What?
Sleep so little and still look so good.
Are you flirting with me?
Commiserating.
- Try to fatten me up?
- What if I am?
Suppose I wanted blueberry.
You had that last night.
You don't fool me, Trevor Reznik.
I have you figured out.
- You do, huh?
- Muhmmm.
What else do you know about me?
That you are lonely.
When you work here as long as I have,
you get to know the type.
Hey, everyone gets lonely, Trevor.
It is nothing to be ashamed of.
How can I be lonely,
when I have you to keep me company?
Check please!